Nurul Uhkrowi

Web Developer

+628977031387 | uhkrowi@gmail.com

https://uhkrowi.github.io

PROFILE

I am a web developer with years of experience, I have passions for all things new and interesting in tech industry. With a `jack-of-all-trades` mindset I have learned and worked as a mobile & desktop app developer, hardware integrator and automation app maker.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dec 2021 - Current

Back End Web Developer

PT Astra International Tbk

- As a body hire from PT BeIT
- Join into Astra team to modify the existing system
- Focusing on tax regulation

Jan 2020 - Current

Front End Web Developer

PT BeIT Inovasi Tiwikrama

- Creating mockups and prototypes
- Design and build UI/UX
- · Integrating with web services, fixing bugs, and doing optimization
- · Do back end stuffs when necessary

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

Front End Web Developer

PT Perjalanan Menembus Galaksi

- Designing and creating web components
- Integrating API

Nov 2017 - Oct 2019

Back End Web Developer

PT Ink & Canvas

- Working closely with clients to establish problem, specifications and system designs
- Coordinating with internal in developing project plans and solutions
- Building, testing, deploying, and maintaining applications
- Refactoring for better performance pupose

Feb 2016 - Nov 2017

Full Stack Web Developer

PT IndoVisual Presentatama

- Collaborating with product management team to design, build, integrate and test systems
- Designing new product elements such as IR and RF connection, CCTV live streaming, hardware integration, and device-to-device communication
- Modifying existing software to fix issues, and improve performance

SKILL

- Go
- Javascript
- NodeJS
- React.js
- Vue.js
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Wordpress
- Microsoft Azure

EDUCATION

2013 - 2016

Information Technology

LP3I Jakarta

PROJECT

Jan 2022 - Mar 2021

Company Profile zumstar.com

Company Profile Website of Zumstar (product of Graha Multimedia Nusantara).

Jan 2022 - Mar 2021

Company Profile gmn.com

Company Profile Website of Graha Multimedia Nusantara.

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Rental Housing

Rental flat, private and public housing in Indonesia for low economic citizen, supply and demand management of properties, facilitate citizen to book and rent house with ease.

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

Booking Room

A mobile application for scheduling meeting with booking available rooms feature, note of MOM, participants invitation, extending meeting time if possible, order meals to the pantry, etc.

Mar 2020 - Apr 2020

Ship Rental Management

Ship rent management aim to ease fishermen to rent ships, including picking type of ship, setting rental period, extending the period, monitoring their payment. the application also helps the owners of rental to manage information about ships, their customers, payments and reports.

Nov 2017 - Oct 2019

English Learning Institution ERP

Resource planning, monitoring and management of many modules that help user to manage data of students, employees, learning processes, payments, etc. Features: Dashboards, Integration of many modules as microservices (academic, human resource, elearning, finance, general data, usermanagement).

Feb 2016 - Nov 2017

Smart Home & Office

Mobile and Web app for managing, controlling and monitoring devices at home e.g lamp/light, door lock, TV, CCTV, air conditioner, curtain, switch, sensors, etc. It's main features are: Managing, Controlling and monitoring devices, Configuration, User management, Role, Permission, etc.